http://onlinespamsolutions.com/privacy-policy

888-369-3375 +1.847.879.1700    LOGIN
HomePricingTry/BuyProductsSpam and Virus BlockingExchange 2013 Email HostingOutbound Spam FilteirngEmail ArchivingMicrosoft Lync HostingWeb Hosting and POP MailDNS HostingHIPAA Enabled FilteringBackup MX ServiceEmail EncrtyptionSupport/Resources
Contact Support"How To" Articles....Issue Articles...Frequently Asked QuestionsTestimonialsGive A TestimonialLink To UsResourcesSite LoginPartners
Partner ProgramAdd A CustomerAbout UsContact
Privacy Policy
WE DON'T SELL YOUR INFORMATION TO ANYONE!
Protecting personal information is a top priority at onlinespamsolutions.com and we have made every effort to provide you piece of mind while submitting private information on our website.
Online SecurityOnlinespamsolutions.com uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) whenever sensitive information is sent or received from your computer. This assures that nobody else can see or alter any personal information in transit.
SSL server authentication allows the browser to confirm a server's identity. Using standard techniques of public-key cryptography, it checks that the server's certificate and public ID are valid and have been issued by a certificate authority (CA) listed in the browser's list of trusted CAs.
An SSL connection encrypts all information sent between the browser and our server. This provides an extremely high degree of confidentiality. In addition, all data sent over an encrypted SSL connection is protected with a mechanism for detecting tampering--that is, for automatically determining whether the data has been altered in transit.
Information CollectionOnlinespamsolutions.com will collect nonpublic personal information about you which is necessary to process your application for service or other requests. The term "nonpublic personal information" refers to information about you which we receive from the sources described below and which is not otherwise lawfully available to the general public.
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from (1) information we receive from you on any service subscription form or any other forms, (2) information we receive when verifying what you have provided on a service subscription form or any other form.
Onlinespamsolutions.com collects only that nonpublic personal information which is customary in the industry and required to provide the products and services requested by our customers.
Information SharingIt is the policy of onlinespamsolutions.com to comply with all laws and regulations regarding use and disclosure of nonpublic personal information relating to individuals or companies. Such information will be used solely to facilitate the products and services requested or as provided or permitted by law.
Onlinespamsolutions.com does not share any nonpublic personal information about you or your company with anyone except as may be required to obtain a requested service, or as authorized by you or required by law.
Onlinespamsolutions.com may partner with third parties to provide specific services. The information that is shared with our third parties is done so in order to obtain any requested service. We share only information that is necessary for a third party to provide these services.
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you or your company to those employees who need to know that information to provide your requested service. Onlinespamsolutions.com maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect your nonpublic personal information.
Identity TheftWe reserve the right to request from customers proof of identity prior to any change of service or request to reset or access personal and confidential information (resetting passwords, change of administration status, etc.). In addition, we reserve the right to withhold from customers any personal and confidential information if they fail to provide any requested documentation needed to verify identity. Identity theft is a serious crime and we will take appropriate measures to prevent it. Any suspected instances of attempted identity theft will be immediately reported to authorities.
ContactOnlinespamsolutions.com may contact you via email, phone, fax, and or traditional mail services during your term of service as needed to provide to you or obtain from you information necessary to continue smooth operation of your requested service.
CookiesOnlinespamsolutions.com may make use of "cookie" technology and web server logs to collect information on how our website is used in order to constantly improve our website and better serve our customers. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our website as they move from one page to another. The web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our website and evaluate our website's visitor capacity. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user friendly manner and continually improve our website to better meet our customers' needs.
Contact usIf you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
We reserve the right to amend our Privacy Policy at any time in which case the changes will be posted on this web page.
Contact
Online Spam Solutions LLC872 S. Milwaukee Ave., Suite 161 Libertyville, Il. 60048United States
support@onlinespamsolutions.com888-369-3375
+1.847.879.1700
Products
Spam & Virus BlockingExchange 2013 Email HostingOutbound Spam FilteringEmail ArchivingMicrosoft Lync HostingWeb Hosting & POP MailDNS HostingHIPAA Enabled FilteringBackup MX ServiceEmail Encryption
Support
Contact SupportIssue ArticlesHow to...FAQTestimonialsGive a TestimonialLink to us
HomePricingTry/BuyProductsSpam and Virus BlockingExchange 2013 Email HostingOutbound Spam FilteirngEmail ArchivingMicrosoft Lync HostingWeb Hosting and POP MailDNS HostingHIPAA Enabled FilteringBackup MX ServiceEmail EncrtyptionSupport/Resources
Contact Support"How To" Articles....Issue Articles...Frequently Asked QuestionsTestimonialsGive A TestimonialLink To UsResourcesSite LoginPartners
Partner ProgramAdd A CustomerAbout UsContact
